+306944629288 tzikoulisathan@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/athanasios-tzikoulis Larisa, Greece

Profile

I am a business minded individual with extreme interest in data based decision making. I have plenty of experience in working and managing several IT projects. I am currently working in the agricultural sector and looking into switching to a Supply Chain and Business Analytics career .

Skills

Technical	Soft skills
MS Excel	Strong work ethics
Tableau Visualization	Problem solving competence
SQL	Determination to meet objectives
Python programming for Data Analysis	Team management
Descriptive - Predictive statistics	Project management
	Self motivation

Working experience

FARM MANAGER. 2005 - UNTIL NOW

Owner and manager of 30 acres of arable land with vegetable, wheat and cotton cultivations. I am responsible for growing and trading the farm's product as well as bookkeeping and delivering all the necessary paperwork.

CO-FOUNDER - IT CONSULTANT. OFFICE NET IT SOLUTIONS, 2008- 2014

My role as an IT consultant was to design, implement and support IT solutions for businesses. More specific I dealt with ERP software installation, configuration and support, network design and implementation and website development using CMS tools.

COMPUTER SCIENCE TUTOR. 2010 - 2015

As a computer tutor, I worked on teaching introduction to computer programming principles as well as computer driving licence certifications for kids, teenagers and adults.

PRODUCT OWNER / PROJECT MANAGER. FORTHEFESTIVALS APP, 2019-2020

As a product owner at "forthefestivals" app I had the responsibility for organizing the team members and assigning the tasks that needed to be fulfilled. I was entitled with the responsibility to make decisions that best fitted user needs and expectations.

Community

BOARD OF DIRECTORS MEMBER. THESGI FARMERS COOPERATION, 2015 - 2020

As an elected member of the BoD of Thesgi in the role of Financial Officer, I was responsible for planning, reporting and executing various duties. Some of these were setting strategic objectives, staff recruitment, client negotiation and budgeting.

Education

T.E.I OF CENTRAL MACEDONIA

BSc. in Computer Science, 2001-2009

HELLENIC OPEN UNIVERSITY

MSc. in Supply Chain Management, 2020-ongoing

Certificates

Google Data Analytics Certificate, 2021

Languages

Greek (Native, excellent use)

English (Proficiency of Michigan, fluent)

German (Mittelstufe, intermediate)